Guide to the Max S. Baucus Papers 1958-2016 (bulk 1974-2014)
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- U.S. House of Representatives: Constituent Correspondence, 1974-1978; Series V; 59.3 linear feet; 9 microfilm reels
  - Social Conditions and Services - Social services, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 115/12)
  - Social Conditions and Services - Social services, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 116/1)
  - Social Conditions and Services - Social services, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 116/2)
  - Social Conditions and Services - Social services, 1978-1979 (Box-folder Series 5 - 116/3)
  - Social Conditions and Services - VISTA (Volunteers in Service to America) Program, 1979 (Box-folder Series 5 - 116/4)
  - Social Conditions and Services - Welfare, 1976-1979 (Box-folder Series 5 - 116/5)
  - Social Conditions and Services - WIC (Women, Infants, and Children) Program, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 116/6)
  - Sports and Recreation - Appropriations, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 116/7)
  - Sports and Recreation - Campgrounds, 1977-1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 116/8)
  - Sports and Recreation - Development funds, 1976-1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 116/9)
  - Sports and Recreation - Forest Service land recreation, 1977-1979 (Box-folder Series 5 - 116/10)
  - Sports and Recreation - High school sports, 1977-1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 116/11)
  - Sports and Recreation - H.J.Res. 599, National Ski Week, 1975 (Box-folder Series 5 - 116/12)
  - Sports and Recreation - H.R. 7239, National Ski Patrol System, Inc., 1975 (Box-folder Series 5 - 116/13)
  - Sports and Recreation - Kalispell Golf Course, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 116/14)
  - Sports and Recreation - National Parks, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 116/15)
  - Sports and Recreation - National Parks, 1977-1979 (Box-folder Series 5 - 116/16)
  - Sports and Recreation - Physical fitness, 1976-1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 116/17)
  - Sports and Recreation - Ski Yellowstone, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 116/18)
  - Sports and Recreation - Ski Yellowstone, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 117/1)
  - Sports and Recreation - Snowmobiles, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 117/2)
  - Sports and Recreation - Snowmobiles, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 117/3)
  - Sports and Recreation - Snowmobiles, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 117/4)
  - Sports and Recreation - Snowmobiles, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 117/5)
  - Sports and Recreation - Snowmobiles, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 117/6)
  - Sports and Recreation - Snowmobiles, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 117/7)
  - Telecommunications - S. 3403, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 117/8)
  - Trade - Meat Import Act, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 117/9)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Aerospace and aviation, 1975 (Box-folder Series 5 - 117/10)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Aerospace and aviation, 1975 (Box-folder Series 5 - 117/11)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Aerospace and aviation, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 117/12)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Aerospace and aviation, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 117/13)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Aerospace and aviation, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 117/14)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Aerospace and aviation, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 117/15)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Aerospace and aviation, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 118/1)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Aerospace and aviation, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 118/2)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Airlines, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 118/3)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Amtrak, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 118/4)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Amtrak, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 118/5)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Amtrak, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 118/6)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Amtrak, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 118/7)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Amtrak, 1978-1979 (Box-folder Series 5 - 118/8)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Amtrak, 1978-1979 (Box-folder Series 5 - 118/9)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Appropriations, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 118/10)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Army Corps of Engineers, 1976-1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 118/11)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Automobiles, 1976-1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 118/12)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Bicycles and motorcycles, 1976-1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 118/13)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Dams and reservoirs, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 118/14)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Dams and reservoirs, 1977-1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 119/1)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Economic Development Administration, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 119/2)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Economic Development Administration, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 119/3)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Economic Development Administration, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 119/4)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Economic Development Administration, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 119/5)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Economic Development Administration, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 119/6)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Economic Development Administration, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 119/7)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Economic Development Administration, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 119/8)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Economic Development Administration, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 119/9)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Economic Development Administration, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 120/1)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Economic Development Administration, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 120/2)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Flood control, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 120/3)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Flood control, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 120/4)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Flood control, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 120/5)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Flood control, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 120/6)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Flood control, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 120/7)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Highways, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 120/8)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Highways, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 120/9)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Highways, 1977-1979 (Box-folder Series 5 - 120/10)
  - Transportation and Public Works - H.R. 5077, Forest Service timber sales, 1975 (Box-folder Series 5 - 120/11)
  - Transportation and Public Works - H.R. 5247, Local Public Works Capitol Development and Investment Act, 1975 (Box-folder Series 5 - 120/12)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Mass transportation, 1976-1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 120/13)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Milwaukee Railroad, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 121/1)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Milwaukee Railroad, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 121/2)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Milwaukee Railroad, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 121/3)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Milwaukee Railroad, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 121/4)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Milwaukee Railroad, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 121/5)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Milwaukee Railroad, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 121/6)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Milwaukee Railroad, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 121/7)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Milwaukee Railroad, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 121/8)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Milwaukee Railroad, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 121/9)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Milwaukee Railroad, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 121/10)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Milwaukee Railroad, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 122/1)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Milwaukee Railroad, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 122/2)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Milwaukee Railroad, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 122/3)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Milwaukee Railroad, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 122/4)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Milwaukee Railroad, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 122/5)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Milwaukee Railroad, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 122/6)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Milwaukee Railroad, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 122/7)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Milwaukee Railroad, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 122/8)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Milwaukee Railroad, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 122/9)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Milwaukee Railroad, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 122/10)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Public works, 1975 (Box-folder Series 5 - 123/1)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Public works, 1975 (Box-folder Series 5 - 123/2)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Public works, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 123/3)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Public works, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 123/4)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Public works, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 123/5)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Public works, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 123/6)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Public works, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 123/7)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Railroads, 1975 (Box-folder Series 5 - 123/8)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Railroads, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 123/9)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Railroads, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 123/10)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Railroads, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 123/11)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Railroads, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 123/12)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Railroads, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 124/1)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Railroads, 1979 (Box-folder Series 5 - 124/2)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Rural transportation, 1976-1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 124/3)
  - Transportation and Public Works - S. 3425, Upper Missouri and Illinois Waterways, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 124/4)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Transportation deregulation, 1975-1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 124/5)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Trucks, 1977-1979 (Box-folder Series 5 - 124/6)
  - Transportation and Public Works - Waterways, 1975-1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 124/7)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1975 (Box-folder Series 5 - 124/8)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1975 (Box-folder Series 5 - 124/9)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1975 (Box-folder Series 5 - 124/10)
  - Veterans Affairs - H.R. 9000, World War I Pension Act, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 124/11)
  - Veterans Affairs - H.R. 9000, World War I Pension Act, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 124/12)
  - Veterans Affairs - H.R. 9000, World War I Pension Act, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 124/13)
  - Form Letters, 1977-1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 124/14)
  - Form Letters, 1977-1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 124/15)
  - Form Letters, 1977-1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 125/1)
  - Form Letters, 1977-1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 125/2)
  - Form Letters, 1977-1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 125/3)
  - Form Letters, 1977-1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 125/4)
  - Mass mailings, 1975 (Box-folder Series 5 - 125/5)
  - Mass mailings, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 125/6)
  - Mass mailings, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 125/7)
  - Mass mailings, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 125/8)
  - Mass mailings, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 125/9)
  - Mass mailings, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 125/10)
  - Mass mailings, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 125/11)
  - Mass mailings, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 125/12)
  - Mass mailings, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 126/1)
  - Mass mailings, 1978 (Box-folder Series 5 - 126/2)
  - Yellow files, 1975 (Box-folder Series 5 - 126/3)
  - Yellow files, Ch, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 126/4)
  - Yellow files, Ch, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 126/5)
  - Yellow files, Co, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 126/6)
  - Yellow files, Co, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 126/7)
  - Yellow files, Co, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 126/8)
  - Yellow files, Cr-Cz, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 126/9)
  - Yellow files, Cr-Cz, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 126/10)
  - Yellow files, Da, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 126/11)
  - Yellow files, Da, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 126/12)
  - Yellow files, De-Do, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 126/13)
  - Yellow files, De-Do, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 126/14)
  - Yellow files, De-Do, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 126/15)
  - Yellow files, Dr-Dz, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 127/1)
  - Yellow files, Ea-El, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 127/2)
  - Yellow files, Eu-Fa, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 127/3)
  - Yellow files, Fa-Fl, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 127/4)
  - Yellow files, Fl-Fr, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 127/5)
  - Yellow files, Fr-Ga, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 127/6)
  - Yellow files, Ga-Gl, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 127/7)
  - Yellow files, Gl-Gr, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 127/8)
  - Yellow files, Gr-Gu, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 127/9)
  - Yellow files Gu-Ha, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 128/1)
  - Yellow files, Han-Has, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 128/2)
  - Yellow files, Has-Hen, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 128/3)
  - Yellow files, Hen-Hin, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 128/4)
  - Yellow files, Hin-Hos, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 128/5)
  - Yellow files, Hoo-Hov, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 128/6)
  - Yellow files, Hov-Hu, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 128/7)
  - Yellow files, I-Ja, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 128/8)
  - Yellow files, Ja-Ji, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 128/9)
  - Yellow files, Joa-Jon, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 129/1)
  - Yellow files, Jon-Ka, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 129/2)
  - Yellow files, Ka-Ke, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 129/3)
  - Yellow files, Ki-Kl, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 129/4)
  - Yellow files, Kl-Kr, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 129/5)
  - Yellow files, Kr-La, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 129/6)
  - Yellow files, La, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 129/7)
  - Yellow files, La-Le, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 129/8)
  - Yellow files, Le-Lo, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 129/9)
  - Yellow files, Lo-Ly, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 130/1)
  - Yellow files, McA, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 130/2)
  - Yellow files, McA, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 130/3)
  - Yellow files, McA, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 130/4)
  - Yellow files, Maa-Mar, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 130/5)
  - Yellow files, Mar-Mi, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 130/6)
  - Yellow files, Mi-Mo, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 130/7)
  - Yellow files, Mon-Mor, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 130/8)
  - Yellow files, Mor-Me, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 130/9)
  - Yellow files, Me-My, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 130/10)
  - Yellow files, Na-Ne, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 131/1)
  - Yellow files, Ni-O, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 131/2)
  - Yellow files, O-Ot, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 131/3)
  - Yellow files, Ot-Pa, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 131/4)
  - Yellow files, Pa-Pe, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 131/5)
  - Yellow files, Pe-Pi, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 131/6)
  - Yellow files, Pi-Pr, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 131/7)
  - Yellow files, Pr-Ra, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 131/8)
  - Yellow files, Ra-Re, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 131/9)
  - Yellow files, Re-Ri, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 132/1)
  - Yellow files, Ro, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 132/2)
  - Yellow files, Ro, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 132/3)
  - Yellow files, Ru, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 132/4)
  - Yellow files, Sa, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 132/5)
  - Yellow files, Sch, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 132/6)
  - Yellow files, Sch, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 132/7)
  - Yellow files, Sci-She, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 132/8)
  - Yellow files, Sei-She, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 132/9)
  - Yellow files, Shi-Sl, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 132/10)
  - Yellow files, Shi-Sl, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 132/11)
  - Yellow files, Sm-So, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 132/12)
  - Yellow files, Sm-So, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 133/1)
  - Yellow files, Sp-Ft, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 133/2)
  - Yellow files, St, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 133/3)
  - Yellow files, St, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 133/4)
  - Yellow files, St-Sz, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 133/5)
  - Yellow files, Ta-To, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 133/6)
  - Yellow files, Ta-To, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 133/7)
  - Yellow files, Th, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 133/8)
  - Yellow files, Th, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 133/9)
  - Yellow files, Ti-To, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 133/10)
  - Yellow files, Tr-Tw, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 133/11)
  - Yellow files, Tw-V, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 133/12)
  - Yellow files, V, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 133/13)
  - Yellow files, Wa, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 134/1)
  - Yellow files, Wa, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 134/2)
  - Yellow files, Wea-Wer, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 134/3)
  - Yellow files, Wes-Wh, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 134/4)
  - Yellow files, Wes-Wh, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 134/5)
  - Yellow files, Wi-Wo, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 134/6)
  - Yellow files, Wi-Wo, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 134/7)
  - Yellow files, Woo-Wy, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 134/8)
  - Yellow files, X-Y, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 134/9)
  - Yellow files, Z, 1976 (Box-folder Series 5 - 134/10)
  - Yellow files, Aa-Am, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 134/11)
  - Yellow files, An-Az, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 134/12)
  - Yellow files, An-Az, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 135/1)
  - Yellow files, Baa-Bar, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 135/2)
  - Yellow files, Baa-Bar, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 135/3)
  - Yellow files, Bas-Beh, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 135/4)
  - Yellow files, Bel-Big, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 135/5)
  - Yellow files, Bel-Big, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 135/6)
  - Yellow files, Bil-Bog, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 135/7)
  - Yellow files, Boh-Br, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 135/8)
  - Yellow files, Boh-Br, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 135/9)
  - Yellow files, Bre-Bro, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 135/10)
  - Yellow files, Bre-Bro, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 135/11)
  - Yellow files, Bru-Bu, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 135/12)
  - Yellow files, Bu-By, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 135/13)
  - Yellow files, Cod-Car, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 136/1)
  - Yellow files, Car-Cat, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 136/2)
  - Yellow files, Cat-Ci, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 136/3)
  - Yellow files, Ch-Co, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 136/4)
  - Yellow files, Coa-Coy, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 136/5)
  - Yellow fiiles, Coa-Coy, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 136/6)
  - Yellow files, Cr-CZ, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 136/7)
  - Yellow files, Da, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 136/8)
  - Yellow files, De-Do, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 136/9)
  - Yellow files, De-Do, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 136/10)
  - Yellow files, Ea-El, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 136/11)
  - Yellow files, Eu-Ew, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 137/1)
  - Yellow files, Fa-Fj, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 137/2)
  - Yellow files, Fl-Fo, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 137/3)
  - Yellow files, Fr-Fu, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 137/4)
  - Yellow files, Ga-Gl, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 137/5)
  - Yellow files, Ge, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 137/6)
  - Yellow files, Gi, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 137/7)
  - Yellow files, Gr-Gw, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 137/8)
  - Yellow files, Gr-Gw, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 137/9)
  - Yellow files, Haa-Hap, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 137/10)
  - Yellow files, Har-Haz, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 137/11)
  - Yellow files, Har-Haz, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 138/1)
  - Yellow files, Hea-Hi, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 138/2)
  - Yellow files, Hi-I, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 138/3)
  - Yellow files, I-Ji, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 138/4)
  - Yellow files, Jo-Ju, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 138/5)
  - Yellow files, Jo-Ju, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 138/6)
  - Yellow files, Ka-Ke, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 138/7)
  - Yellow files, Ke-Ki, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 138/8)
  - Yellow files, Ki-Kn, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 138/9)
  - Yellow files, Ko-Kr, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 138/10)
  - Yellow files, Kra-Kru, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 138/11)
  - Yellow files, Kr-Ky, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 138/12)
  - Yellow files, Laa-Lar, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 138/13)
  - Yellow files, Lar-Le, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 139/1)
  - Yellow files, Le-Li, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 139/2)
  - Yellow files, Ll-Ly, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 139/3)
  - Yellow files, Maa-Man, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 139/4)
  - Yellow files, Mar-Mau, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 139/5)
  - Yellow files, Mav-Maz, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 139/6)
  - Yellow files, McA-McW, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 139/7)
  - Yellow files, McA-McW, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 139/8)
  - Yellow files, McA-McW, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 139/9)
  - Yellow files, Me, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 139/10)
  - Yellow files, Mi, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 139/11)
  - Yellow files, Moc-Mor, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 140/1)
  - Yellow files, Mos-My, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 140/2)
  - Yellow files, Na-Ng, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 140/3)
  - Yellow files, Ni-Ny, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 140/4)
  - Yellow files, O'B-O'T, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 140/5)
  - Yellow files, O, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 140/6)
  - Yellow files, Pa-Pf, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 140/7)
  - Yellow files, Pa-Pf, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 140/8)
  - Yellow files, Ph-Pu, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 140/9)
  - Yellow files, Ph-Pu, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 140/10)
  - Yellow files, Q, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 141/1)
  - Yellow files, Ra, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 141/2)
  - Yellow files, Re-Ri, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 141/3)
  - Yellow files, Re-Ri, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 141/4)
  - Yellow files, Ro, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 141/5)
  - Yellow files, Ro, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 141/6)
  - Yellow files, Ru-Ry, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 141/7)
  - Yellow files, Sa-Sc, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 141/8)
  - Yellow files, Sc-Se, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 141/9)
  - Yellow files, Se-Sh, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 141/10)
  - Yellow files, Shi-Sl, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 141/11)
  - Yellow files, Sm-So, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 141/12)
  - Yellow files, Sp-St, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 142/1)
  - Yellow files, St, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 142/2)
  - Yellow files, St-Sw, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 142/3)
  - Yellow files, Sw-Te, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 142/4)
  - Yellow files, Th-To, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 142/5)
  - Yellow files, To-Tu, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 142/6)
  - Yellow files, Tu-Vi, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 142/7)
  - Yellow files, Vi-Wa, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 142/8)
  - Yellow files, Wa, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 142/9)
  - Yellow files, We-Wh, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 142/10)
  - Yellow files, Wh-Wi, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 143/1)
  - Yellow files, Wi-Wo, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 143/2)
  - Yellow files, Wr-Wy, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 143/3)
  - Yellow files, Y-Zi, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 143/4)
  - Yellow files, Zi-Zy, 1977 (Box-folder Series 5 - 143/5)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 9 reels microfilm, 1976 (Reels Series 5 - microfilm)
- U.S. House of Representatives: Legislative, 1974-1979; Series VI; 16.2 linear feet; 76.3 megabytes
  This series contains legislative materials relating to Max Baucus’s time in the U.S. House of Representatives, which present a clear view of the legislative process from start to finish. These files outline the scope and extent of Baucus’s legislative work throughout his first two terms in Congress, generated and gathered by both Baucus and his staffers. Such work included policy research and development, correspondence and collaboration with members of Congress and other stakeholders, Committee hearings and deliberations, gathering and collating data, and drafting and editing legislation.